Susan Beno

Tel: (203) 895-0758 | Email: beno.susan@gmail.com | Location: Branford, CT

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/susan-beno/ Portfolio: https://suebee21.github.io/Portfolio/ GitHub: github.com/SueBee21

SUMMARY

A January 2021 graduate of the University of Connecticut's Full Stack Web Development certificate program seeking to capitalize on 13 years of career experience as a clinical social worker and who prefers to join a programming team in order to solve problems and think critically; passionate about developing intuitive and accessible applications in order to create a 1st-in-class user experience.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Applications: MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, Epic Languages: NodeJS, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, React Native, GIT, GitHub, MongoDB Skills: Microsoft Office, Writing, Management, Creative Problem Solving, Empathy, Time Management

PROJECTS

Personnel Manager— employee content management system utilizing MySQL and Node

GitHub: https://github.com/SueBee21/personnel-manager

Burger Builder — simple restaurant app utilizing MySQL and node dependencies with Heroku deployment

GitHub: https://github.com/SueBee21/burger-builder

Deployed Application: https://burger-builder-0.herokuapp.com/

Employee Finder - *employee database using React and web-based API*

GitHub: https://github.com/SueBee21/employee-finder

Deployed Application: https://suebee21.github.io/employee-finder/

Budget-to-Go – progressive web application using MongoDB

GitHub: https://github.com/SueBee21/budget-to-go

Deployed Application: https://budget-to-go.herokuapp.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Yale New Haven Health, New Haven, CT— Clinical Social Worker II October 2017 - PRESENT

- Acts as a member of the cross-departmental medical team to conduct patient assessments and provide crisis and intervention treatment decisions when problem solving on behalf of patients.
- Provides technical support to staff around the use of electronic medical records as a member of the Documentation and Training Committee; trained as an *Epic Super User*.
- Recipient of the 2019 Smilow Luminary Award for Excellence in Patient Experience.
- **Board of Directors:** Connecticut Social Work Oncology Group (member since 2016).

CancerCare, Inc, Norwalk, CT — Clinical Supervisor.
— Children's Program Coordinator

November 2015 - September 2017

April 2015- October 2015

- Managed a staff of social workers, volunteers, and interns for the non-profit organization's regional office.
- Coordinated and delivered program deliverables
- Built relationships with community partners in order to develop, collaborate, and implement community health initiatives.
- Assessed client needs to decide appropriate therapy services; partnered with clients to develop goals.
- Spearheaded program development for identified client population including outreach and collaboration with community partners.

Parent Child Resource Center, Derby, CT — Mental Health Clinician December 2012- March 2015

- Utilized empathy and active listening to partner with clients and develop shared goals for provision of mental health and trauma-therapy sessions.
- Increased successful client outcomes through cross-functional collaboration while working in a team format of patient-care model.

Edwin Gould Services, Brooklyn, NY — Crisis Intervention Supervisor.

— Crisis Intervention Clinician

May 2010- August 2012

June 2008- April 2010

- Managed day-to-day operations of the agency's Mental Health unit throughout four regional sites.
- Supervised staff activities and monitored outcomes of deliverable services.
- Developed client needs assessments and established goals, often in partnership with guardians.

EDUCATION

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development — The University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT

• Completed a 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Masters in Social Work — Southern Connecticut State University, New Haven, CT

Bachelors in Social Work — Taylor University, Upland, IN